hey this is russell encore of
claimsecrets.com you clicked on my on my
video because you were searching for a
phone number for prudential insurance
for
auto home or rv or watercraft or
personal liability or something like
that in the property and casualty lines
i've got the number for you here it is
346-3778 it's listed down below this
video so don't worry about catching it
because of what i you know verbally
but before you call them let me tell you
why you should not call them quite yet
as soon as you file your claim you and
the insurance company are going to go in
different directions they want to pay
you the least amount that you'll accept
for this loss
and
you want to collect the most that you
can get under your policy so you've got
a problem right away but folks it could
get worse
because you're not a claim specialist
the insurance company knows the entire
claims process and you don't
you need to know the claims process
before it starts because once you call
that number and report your claim the
insurance company may start the ball
rolling the same day and if you do
something wrong early in the claims
process because you didn't know any
better it could cost you thousands they
could even deny your claim so think
about like the tax think of it like your
tax return you don't know the whole tax
code who could so
don't you get a tax expert to maximize
your benefits well it's the same thing
here
so before you report your claim i want
you to read my book entitled insurance
claims secrets reveal i will personally
show you how to take control of your
claim
and add hundreds or even thousands more
dollars to your claim settlement let me
give you an example from the book in
most cases or in most claims
the adjuster is going to ask you for a
recorded statement about the loss
in my book i'll show you how to give a
correct recorded statement without
giving away your legal rights
so don't call the insurance company
today read my book first you can get
this book as an ebook and you can call
the insurance company tomorrow go to
claimsecrets.com the link is right below
do it now this is russell encore if you
need to get a hold of me and get some
questions answered contact me through
the website thanks good luck